Guide to the Guerrilla TV Archive 1965-1997 MSS 138 MSS.138
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Audio Recordings
  - Subseries B: Conferences
    - ALA "Video: An Alternative Information Service", June 1980. Part 2 of 2, 138.0163 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0163, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0163)
      Audiocassette, unmarked, 43 min.
    - ALA 1980 Annual Conference. Part 1 of 5, 138.0164 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0164, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0164)
      Audiocassette, unmarked, 93 min.
    - ALA 1980 Annual Conference. Part 2 of 5, 138.0165 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0165, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0165)
      Audiocassette, unmarked, 89 min.
    - ALA 1980 Annual Conference. Part 3 of 5, 138.0166 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0166, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0166)
    - ALA 1980 Annual Conference. Part 4 of 5, 138.0167 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0167, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0167)
      Audiocassette, unmarked, 91 min.
    - ALA 1980 Annual Conference. Part 5 of 5, 138.0168 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0168, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0168)
      Audiocassette, unmarked, 26 min.
    - Anthology Film Archives "Video Art History" May 10, 1984. Part 1 of 2, 138.0169 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0169, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0169)
      Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, 92 min.
    - Anthology Film Archives "Video Art History" May 10, 1984. Part 2 of 2, 138.0170 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0170, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0170)
      Audiocassette, Sony LNX90, 49 min.
    - Anthology Film Archives, Video Symposia III, participants include Bill Creston, David Cort, Les Levine, Nam June Paik, Paul Ryan, Ira Schneider, Aldo Tambellini. Moderated by Davidson Gigliotti, April 11, 1985. Part 1 of 3, 138.0171 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0171, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0171)
      Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 93 min.
    - Anthology Film Archives, Video Symposia III, participants include Bill Creston, David Cort, Les Levine, Nam June Paik, Paul Ryan, Ira Schneider, Aldo Tambellini. Moderated by Davidson Gigliotti, April 11, 1985. Part 2 of 3, 138.0172 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0172, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0172)
      Audiocassette, Sony CHF90, 45 min.
    - Anthology Film Archives, Video Symposia III, participants include Bill Creston, David Cort, Les Levine, Nam June Paik, Paul Ryan, Ira Schneider, Aldo Tambellini. Moderated by Davidson Gigliotti, April 11, 1985. Part 3 of 3, 138.0173 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0173, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0173)
      Audiocassette, Sony CHF90, 41 min.
    - Anthology Film Archives Guerrilla Television Symposium. Participants include Ben Levin, Bill Stevens, Susan Milano, John Reilly, Skip Blumberg. Moderated by Deirdre Boyle, November 14, 1985. Part 1 of 2, 138.0174 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0174, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0174)
      Audiocassette, Sony CHF90, 94 min.
    - Anthology Film Archives Guerrilla Television Symposium. Participants include Ben Levin, Bill Stevens, Susan Milano, John Reilly, Skip Blumberg. Moderated by Deirdre Boyle, November 14, 1985. Part 2 of 2, 138.0175 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0175, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0175)
      Audiocassette, TDK D30, 5 min.
    - Community TV USA segment on Broadside TV., 1976; 138.0176 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0176, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0176)
      Audiocassette, TDK AD-C60, 59 min.
    - KPFK Long Beach LBMA Show Jay Kugleman interview with Deirdre Boyle., 1986; 138.0177 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0177, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0177)
      Audiocassette, Maxell UR60, 59 min.
    - Low Power TV Discussion with Parry Teasdale et al, undated; 138.0178 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0178, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0178)
      Audiocassette, TDK AD90, 95 min.
    - National Public Radio "Morning Edition. Celeste Wesson interviews Deirdre Boyle about LBMA Documentary show, March 10, 1986, 138.0179 (Box 14, Cassette 138.0179, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0179)
      Audiocassette, TDK SA90, 37 min.
    - New School and MoMA "Documentary Video: Subject to Change" with Deirdre Boyle. Part 1 of 2, 1988; 138.018 (Box 14, Cassette 138.018, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.018)
      Audiocassette, TDK D90, 95 min.
    - New School and MoMA "Documentary Video: Subject to Change" with Deirdre Boyle. Part 2 of 2, 1988; 138.0181 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0181, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0181)
      Audiocassette, Maxell UR90, 94 min.
    - Port Washington Library "Video at the Library" participants include Deirdre Boyle, Karen Ranucci and Edin Velez, April 6, 1992. Part 1 of 2, 138.0182 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0182, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0182)
      Audiocassette, 90min. unmarked, 95 min.
    - Port Washington Library "Video at the Library" participants include Deirdre Boyle, Karen Ranucci and Edin Velez, April 6, 1992. Part 2 of 2, 138.0183 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0183, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0183)
      Audiocassette, 60min. unmarked, 63 min.
    - Port Washington Library "Video at the Library" participants include Deirdre Boyle and Skip Blumberg, April 10, 1992., 138.0184 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0184, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0184)
      Audiocassette, 90min. unmarked, 0 min.
    - Port Washington Library "Video at the Library" participants include Deirdre Boyle and Shalom Gorewitz, April 14, 1992, 138.0185 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0185, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0185)
      Audiocassette, 90min unmarked, 49 min.
    - Port Washington Library "Video at the Library" participants include Deirdre Boyle and Staff, April 20, 1992., 138.0186 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0186, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0186)
      Audiocassette, 90min unmarked, 92 min.
    - Video South Conference "Community and Culture: How Video Creates New Perspectives.", 1977-1978; 138.0187 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0187, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0187)
      Audiocassette, TDK AD-C90, 71 min.
    - Video South Conference "Where Do We Go From Here?", 1977-1978; 138.0188 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0188, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0188)
      Audiocassette, TDK AD-C90, 68 min.
  - Subseries C: Other Interviews [not Subject to Change]
    - Side A: Karen Cooper, Hope Ryden, December 6, 19zz; Side B:Bill Greaves, December 8, 19zz, undated; 138.0189 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0189, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0189)
      Audiocassette, TDK D IECI Type I, 93 min.
    - Peter Forgacs, New School Class, March 16,1995., 138.0190 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0190, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0190)
      Audiocassette, TDK D90, 70 min.
    - Pare Lorentz at Pacific Film Archive. November 10, 1976, 138.0196 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0196, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0196)
      Audiocassette, Fuji DR-1, 63 min.
    - Side A:Bob Summers and Penee Bender; Side B: Gringo in Mañanaland, September 22, 1995, 138.0191 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0191, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0191)
    - DeeDee Halleck, "Gringo in Mañanaland," September 22, 1995., 138.0192 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0192, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0192)
      Audiocassette, TDK D90, 94 min.
    - Fred Wiseman, January 28, 2000., 138.0193 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0193, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0193)
      Audiocassette, TDK D90, 86 min.
  - Subseries D: Deirdre Boyle's Trip to Australia
    - Peter Gilles discusses Metro Television-Sydney, June 18, 1995., 138.0194 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0194, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0194)
      Audiocassette, TDK D90, 81 min.
    - Bruce Goldstein and Steven Sbarge discuss Film Australia Sydney, June 1995., 138.0196 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0195, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0195)
      Audiocassette, TDK D90, 83 min.
    - Bruce Moir, discusses Film Australia Sydney. June 1995., 138.0197 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0197, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0197)
    - Cathy Robinson discusses the Australian Film Commission. June 1995., 138.0198 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0198, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0198)
      Audiocassette, TDK D90, 71 min.
    - Greg Smith discusses NSW Film and TV office, Victoria Trede discusses Miramax and Kerrie McGovern discusses NSW. June 13, 1995., 138.0199 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0199, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0199)
    - Tait. June 23, 1995, 138.0200 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0200, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0200)
      Audiocassette, TDK D90, 79 min.
    - Robin Wright discusses Film Victoria, Ruth Jones discusses Australian Film Institute and Deb Verhoeven discusses International Documentary Conference. June 21, 1995., 138.0201 (Box 15, Cassette 138.0201, E-records fales_mss138, E-records 138.0201)
      Audiocassette, TDK D90, 65 min.
- Series VIII: Printed Materials
  Following is a list of the printed materials that have been kept with the Guerrilla TV Archive. To see a list of the printed materials that have been separated from the collection, and cataloged individually, see the Separated Material portion of this finding aid.
  Materials are organized into 3 subseries: Subseries A, Books, Studies and Reports; Subseries B, Periodicals; Subseries C, Hong Kong International Film Festival Materials.
  - Subseries A: Books, Studies and Reports
    - European Television Report [begins on p.5], undated (Box 11, Folder 293)
    - Miscellaneous Authors. Bound articles., 1970-1984 (Box 11, Folder 292)
    - "Primary" articles., ca. 1992 (Box 11, Folder 294)
  - Subseries B: Periodicals and Newsletters
    - American Film Institute Education Newsletter 4:1, 5:1, 6:1., 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 295)
    - Art Com, #21, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 296)
    - Cineaste: America's Leading Magazine on the Art and Politics of the Cinema, 26:2., 2001 (Box 11, Folder 297)
    - CineVue: A Publication of Asian Cinevision. 3:1 [located in oversize box], 1988 (Box 11, Folder 298)
    - The CoEvolution Quarterly, Winter 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 299)
    - Community Television Review, January and October 1981, Winter 1982, Winter 1983., 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 300)
    - Community Video Report [became TeleVisions] 1:1-4, 2:1-2., 1973 (Box 11, Folder 301)
    - Current: For People in Public Telecommunications. 7:16 [located in oversize box], 1988 (Box 11, Folder 302)
    - CVRP Patch Panel: The Newsletter of the California Video Resource Project. 2:6, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 303)
    - The Dial, July 1981 (Box 11, Folder 304)
    - et cetera. A Journal devoted to the role of symbols in human behavior. June 1977 (Box 11, Folder 305)
    - Global Village Air Time: A Newsletter for Independent Producers and Broadcasters. 1:1-4, 1:6-10, ca. 1980 (Box 11, Folder 306)
    - Image Newsletter 5:13 and 6:6, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 307)
    - The Independent Gazette: Journal of Independent Film and Video Artists, 1:1 [located in oversize materials], 1976 (Box 11, Folder 308)
    - LBMAVIDEO Long Beach Museum of Art Video: Museum 1:3, 2:1-6, 3:1, 3:2, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 309)
    - Performance, #3, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 310)
    - QuarterPoint: The Focal Point Media Center Newsletter, Fall 1983 (Box 11, Folder 311)
    - Scan: Chicago Editing Center. 3:5, 4:1-5, 6:1-2., 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 312)
    - Southwest Media Review. v.2, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 313)
    - Southwestern Alternate Media Project Newsletter. 1:1, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 314)
    - Synapse TeleCast (Syracuse University). March and June 1979. Two undated copies [one perhaps from July 1979 and the other December 1978?], ca. 1979 (Box 11, Folder 315)
    - Television Laboratory at WNET-13: Vision News, Winter 1977 [located in oversize box] (Box 11, Folder 316)
    - TV Magazine, Spring 1983 (Box 11, Folder 317)
    - University Film Study Center Newsletter, October 1975 (Box 11, Folder 318)
    - Video and the Arts, Winter 1986 (Box 11, Folder 319)
    - Video Guide [see oversize materials], ca. 1980 (Box 11, Folder 320)
    - Video Tools. 1:1 and no.2. [photocopies; see oversize], 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 321)
  - Subseries C: Hong Kong Cinema
    - Hong Kong Film Archive Programmes, 1999-2002 (Box 11, Folder 322)
    - Hong Kong Film Archive Newsletters, 2003-2007 (Box 19, Folder 1-5)
    - Hong Kong Film Archive Publication Catalogs, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Oversize Materials: Series I
  These boxes contain oversized materials from Series I: Files, primarily posters, fliers and newspapers.
  - Alan and Susan Raymond, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Tom Zafian, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Washington Community Video Center, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Southwest Alternate Media Project (SWAMP), undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Image Atlanta, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - 7th annual Global Village Documentary Festival, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - 8th annual Global Village Documentary Festival, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - 11th annual Global Village Documentary Festival, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - 12th annual Global Village Documentary Festival, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Global Village, undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Anthology Film Archives, undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Athens Video Festival, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Athens Video Festival, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 32B)
  - Athens Video Festival, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - "Perspectives on Community Video" DCTV Festival, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - DCTV Community Video Festival, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - American Film Institute (AFI) National Video Festival, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - AFI National Video Festival, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA) Video Publicity, undated (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Whitney Video Publicity, undated (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous Video Exhibitions, undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - The Kitchen, Fliers and Publicity, undated (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Long Beach Museum Video Publicity, undated (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, H. Klein, undated (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Independent Documentary Fund (IDF) and TV Lab, undated (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Bay Area Video Coalition (BAVC), undated (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Women's Video, undated (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Fred Simon, undated (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Stevenson Palfi, undated (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Mike Hazard, undated (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Miscellaneous Video Art, undated (Box 17, Folder 85)
  - Video Artists A-L, undated (Box 17, Folder 86)
  - Video Artists M-Z, undated (Box 17, Folder 87)
  - Canadian Video, undated (Box 17, Folder 89)
  - Alvarez, Kolker and New Orleans Video Access Center (NOVAC), undated (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - Jon Alpert articles and catalogues, undated (Box 17, Folder 93)
  - Appalshop, undated (Box 17, Folder 95)
  - Ithaca Video Festival, 1981-1995 (Box 17, Folder 110)
  - Mobius Video, San Francisco, undated (Box 17, Folder 114)
  - New Orleans Video Access Center (NOVAC), undated (Box 17, Folder 116)
  - Optic Nerve, undated (Box 17, Folder 121)
  - Paper Tiger TV, Deep Dish TV and DeeDee Halleck, undated (Box 17, Folder 122)
  - Paul Ryan, undated (Box 17, Folder 132)
  - TVTV Conventions, undated (Box 17, Folder 141)
  - San Francisco Video Festival, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 133)
  - TVTV Adland, undated (Box 17, Folder 148)
  - Video Free America, undated (Box 17, Folder 152)
  - Videofreex, Media Bus, Lanesville, undated (Box 17, Folder 153)
  - Miscellaneous and Details: Display Selection, undated (Box 17, Folder 157)
  - Miscellaneous and Details: Video and TV Newspaper Articles, undated (Box 17, Folder 161)
  - Cable and Public Access TV: Basic Cable, undated (Box 17, Folder 163)
  - Cable and Public Access TV: National Federation of Local Cable Programmers (NFLCP), undated (Box 17, Folder 166)
- Oversize Materials: Series V
  These boxes contain oversized materials from Series V: Photographs, primarily large format photographs and images used in the book Subject to Change: Guerrilla Television Revisited
  - Paper filed amid video stills. [corresponding photographs located in boxes 8 and 9], undated (Box 17, Folder 261)
  - Photographs and Images used in Subject to Change: Guerrilla Television Revisited, undated (Box 17, Folder data_value_missing_d1df31bc9b27e0428714a0232612bbbc)
- Oversize Materials: Series VIIIB
  Oversize materials from Series VIIIB: Printed Materials primarily include large newspapers and magazines.
  - CineVue [Asian Cinevision], 1988 (Box 18, Folder 298)
  - Community Video Report, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 301)
  - Current, September 1988 (Box 18, Folder 302)
  - The Independent Gazette, July 1976 (Box 18, Folder 308)
  - The Television Laboratory at WNET-13: Vision News, Winter 1977 (Box 18, Folder 316)
  - Video Guide, Nov.'78-Jan.'79, 2:4-5, 3:2, 5:1, 5:2, ca. 1980 (Box 18, Folder 320)
  - Video Tools #1 and #2, photocopies, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 321)